https://learningexpress.com/terms-conditions/

Terms & Conditions
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
Terms and Conditions Apply.
Read the full “Terms and Conditions.” by clicking here.
Skip to main content
Accessibility
Search Icon
Search:
Toggle navigation
Just Arrived!
Cart $0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Subtotal:
Franchise Info
Just Arrived!
Terms & Conditions
Welcome to the LE Toys Dot Com web site. The goal of this web site is to provide access to our selection of toys, books, games and gifts to as wide an audience as possible. To ensure a safe, pleasant environment for all of our users, we have established these Terms of Use. In this way, you will know what you expect from us and what we expect from you. By accessing any areas of LearningExpress.com, you agree to abide by the terms set forth below.
Terms & Conditions Updates
Learning Express reserves the right to update or modify these Terms & Conditions at any time without prior notice. Updates will be posted to this page and are effective upon posting.
Conduct
Any conduct by you that restricts or inhibits any other user from using or enjoying LearningExpress.com will not be permitted. You agree to use LearningExpress.com in accordance with these Terms of Use and only for lawful purposes. You are prohibited from posting on or transmitting through LearningExpress.com any unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, sexually explicit, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable material of any kind, including but not limited to any material that encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any applicable local, state, national, or international law.
Trademarks
All the Content on this website is subject to copyright, trademark, service mark, trade dress and other intellectual property rights. All site design, text, typefaces, graphics, videos, sound, interfaces and their arrangements are the property of LearningExpress.com. You may only download, print and store selected portions of the Content for your personal, non-commercial use where it is related to shopping from this site and placing an order.
Disclaimers and Limitation of Liability
You expressly agree that use of LearningExpress.com is at your sole risk and LearningExpress.com shall not be liable for any damages of any kind related to your use of this website. The website and content are provided on an "as is" basis without warranty of any kind, including implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.
LearningExpress.com makes every attempt to ensure that the content on this website is complete, current and accurate. However, we cannot guarantee that the information contained on this website will not contain errors, inaccuracies or omissions. Such errors may relate to product availability, price or product description. LearningExpress.com reserves the right to refuse or cancel any orders containing any error, inaccuracy or omission. This may include orders that have been submitted, confirmed or charged to your credit card. If an order is canceled after your credit card has been charged, it will be fully refunded.   Under no circumstances shall the company or any other party involved in creating, producing, or distributing LEARNINGEXPRESS.COM be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages, including without limitation, lost profits that result from the use of or inability to use LEARNINGEXPRESS.COM, including but not limited to reliance by you on any information obtained from LEARNINGEXPRESS.COM or that result from mistakes, omissions, interruptions, deletion of files or email, errors, defects, viruses, delays in operation or transmission, or any failure of performance, whether or not resulting from acts of god, communications failure, theft, destruction, or unauthorized access to the company's records, programs, or services. You hereby acknowledge that this paragraph shall apply to all content, merchandise, and services available through LEARNINGEXPRESS.COM. Because some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, in such states liability is limited to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Arbitration Agreement
Take note that by accessing the material on this website you are agreeing to our terms and conditions, including an agreement to arbitrate any claims related to the website. You can read the agreement to arbitrate by clicking this link “Arbitration Agreement.”
Hyperlinks to Other Websites
This website may contain links to other websites that are not owned or operated by LearningExpress.com, although such sites may have an affiliation with LearningExpress.com. You acknowledge that LearningExpress.com is not responsible for the availability of or content located on any Third Party Site.
Distribution/Uploading of Third Party Content
Any Content you submit or make available for inclusion on the website shall become the sole property of LearningExpress.com. Regarding all such Content, including, without limitation, creative ideas, suggestions, content, postings, artwork, photograph, material or other submissions (collectively, "User Submissions"), you grant the Company the right to use, reproduce, disclose, publish and distribute any material you submit for any reason without compensation.
No User Submissions, regardless of how they may be marked, will be received by us in confidence, nor shall they be subject to any express or implied obligation of confidentially. Neither the Company, nor its Affiliates, nor their respective officers, directors, agents or employees shall be liable for any use or disclosure of any User Submissions.
In addition, the Company may, in our sole discretion, at any time and without prior notice to you, suspend or terminate any public forum, any other portion of the Web Site, or the subscription or registration of any user who violates any of these terms and conditions of use, any of the rules, regulations or guidelines or for any other behavior that we in our sole discretion believe is inappropriate.
Privacy Policy
At the Company, we recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers and members and have established a privacy policy as a result. In our Privacy Policy we describe why we gather customer and member information, what information we collect, how we collect it, what we use the information for and how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information. We encourage you to carefully read our Privacy Policy. Click here to read our Privacy Policy.
My Account
Create an Account
Log In
Gift Card Balance
Order Status
About Us
Store Locations
The Learning Express Story
Terms and Conditions Apply.
Read the full “Terms and Conditions.” by clicking here.
Accept
Close
